you
okay maybe see what I'm actually
speeding why I a new system everybody
very good
okay so right now what I'm trying to do
is I'm trying to make sure that I have
the ability to remain engaged with you
all during this very strange situation
and I'm trying to develop the ability to
not only speak to you but also to use
other tools for example whiteboarding
sessions multi-streaming and so
communication is before a big issue for
me at the moment because I can't easily
necessarily get to the studio that I was
using for the portal and I'm using you
sort of jerry-rigged situation but
casting English you can helping me along
by a public figure this out now one of
the things that I wanted to get at
there's a very important topic which is
what is the difficulty in communicating
to a very very mascot and I think this
is something I'm just completely
unprepared for but luckily it seems like
everyone else is completely unprepared
for it as well I've gotten some recent
comments about why speak and equipted
style why use instructions in force now
why this
throw the problem back to the audience
and that issue is that it's very
important to me to communicate that we
are trying to do something which is to
bring people together whenever you try
to bring people together you have a very
difficult problem and is they have very
different expectations one of the things
that I've come to believe is that almost
all of us are mapping each other back to
very simplified position but we keep in
our mind like oh I get it you're you're
in hand cap or you're you're a free
market libertarian or I get it you're a
radical leftist and in so doing what we
keep doing is destroying any kind of
individuality that is positive and this
is extremely disconcerting to me how do
we communicate when we're communicating
the scale we can't filter the audience
part of what I've been trying to do if
the portal is to build a world in which
people are somewhat self selected by
their seriousness of purpose and their
willingness to sort of suspend for a
period of time I needed to exactly say
well what is or is not going on and I
think without the ability to sort of go
meta and to have a suspension of me or
us to be able to say exactly what
somebody's saying we're constantly
functioning a straitjacket so this is a
topic that I'm hoping to explore shortly
right now I'm trying to stream currently
on Twitch on Facebook and on suddenly
I'm showing up on the forum that I'm
showing up I am
apparently not getting this go live to
work exactly as well as I could forgive
me and bear with me but I'm trying my
best and I don't exactly know what it is
it is going wrong and my threat set up
so I'll try to work that out if just to
close out what it is that I was trying
to get at I think that many of you are
asking me questions about how we should
be trying to communicate when there is
so much distrust and so much inability
to hear another person needs to point if
they say anything that we know in our
heart of hearts to be false and so it's
almost impossible for us to communicate
at scale
I will endeavor to try to do better but
I want to ask all of you just actually
bear with me and be kinder and be more
understanding and forgiving and if you
see something that you don't like try to
imagine the number of different people
but I'm trying to communicate with at
once and I'm gonna start pushing back on
it's important this is what Dave
Chappelle did it's important to stop
trying to drive people crazy who are
venturing into the public arena and
saying hey I'm trying my best integrate
a bunch to be very confusing
contradictory and very high-level source
and I will endeavor to do well by deal
but I wanted to communicate that I
believe that one of the problems were
having is that it's simply too difficult
to communicate people on the far right
the far left be confused middle people
from other countries and in part some of
these communication style styles have
developed out of a need to communicate
the thousands of people who share
totally different lives so bear with me
I'm trying my best and I will be back
with you as I try to work out the
streaming platforms this has been
another experiment but if if you could I
would very much appreciate feedback on
the corona
section of the most recent portal
episode with James O'Keefe we did a
housekeeping section I tried to talk him
about the difficulty of figuring out
what to privilege and really don't seem
to be able to come up with an expert
consensus as to exactly what we're going
so I want to say thank you all very much
and I will endeavor to get this
multi-platform streaming system hooked
up with whiteboard so that I can begin
to give more standard presentations
during this time they're all locked out
I really appreciate you guys all bearing
with me as a 54 year old guy tries to
figure out restreaming without a lot of
experience with World of Warcraft or
ecology
you
I finally has found the screen that was
actually operating the video